[
    {
        "question" : "Question 1",
        "answer" : "1",
        "a1": "This is the answer",
        "a2": "This isn't the answer",
        "a3": "Wrong Answer",
        "a4": "first one is the answer"

    },
    {
        "question" : "Which league of legends character says 'Your will, my hands?'",
        "answer" : "2",
        "a1": "Sett",
        "a2": "Lee Sin",
        "a3": "Vi",
        "a4": "Kassadin"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Very Long question ifoisahnfoahegouhaowguawogh hgoawehgnoaw gbidagbowuagoabwrgou oawrugbnoawebugowaeubg oawdenugjoaerngobaubg jaorgbnueajgb",
        "answer" : "1",
        "a1": "this is the answer",
        "a2": "???",
        "a3": "huh??",
        "a4": "yeah..."
    },
    {
        "question" : "What frontend library was used to create this application?",
        "answer" : "3",
        "a1": "MongoDB",
        "a2": "Express.js",
        "a3": "React",
        "a4": "Node.js"
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is the capital of Canada?",
        "answer" : "4",
        "a1": "Toronto",
        "a2": "Vancouver",
        "a3": "Montreal",
        "a4": "Ottawa"
    },
    {
        "question" : "What car is nicknamed the Hachi-Roku?",
        "answer" : "2",
        "a1": "Nissan Skyline R34",
        "a2": "Toyota AE86",
        "a3": "Toyota Supra",
        "a4": "Honda S2000"
    },
    {
        "question" : "What hololive virtual youtuber calls their fans 'Fandead' ",
        "answer" : "4",
        "a1": "Pekora",
        "a2": "Flare",
        "a3": "Aqua",
        "a4": "Rushia"
    },
    {
        "question" : "How many fingers does a typical hand have?",
        "answer" : "2",
        "a1": "4",
        "a2": "5",
        "a3": "10",
        "a4": "32"
    },
    {
        "question" : "What is the lowest level programming language listed here?",
        "answer" : "1",
        "a1": "Assembly",
        "a2": "C",
        "a3": "Python",
        "a4": "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        "question" : "Answer is 4",
        "answer" : "4",
        "a1": "one",
        "a2": "two",
        "a3": "three",
        "a4": "four!"
    }
]